A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller personal papers, Possessions, Series K FA011
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Property, 810-812 Fifth Avenue, George A. Fuller agreements, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 238)
- Property, 810-812 Fifth Avenue, George A. Fuller agreements, 1964-1971 (Box 19, Folder 239)
- Property, 810-812 Fifth Avenue, storage for furnishings and Museum of Primitive Art delivery, 1963 March (Box 19, Folder 240)
- Property, 810-812 Fifth Avenue, work orders--alterations, 1962 December-1963 June (Box 19, Folder 241)
- Property, 810-812 Fifth Avenue, work orders--alterations, 1963 July-December (Box 20, Folder 242)
- Property, 810-812 Fifth Avenue, work orders--alterations, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 243)
- Property, 810-812 Fifth Avenue, orders and plans for alterations, 1964-1971 (Box 20, Folder 244)
- Property, 810-812 Fifth Avenue, fallout shelters, 1960-1968 (Box 20, Folder 245)
- Property, 810-812 Fifth Avenue, security and alarms, 1952-1970 (Box 20, Folder 246)
- Property, 810-812 Fifth Avenue penthouse, purchase, 1934 (Box 20, Folder 247)
- Property, 810-812 Fifth Avenue penthouse, alterations, 1947-1957 (Box 20, Folder 248)
- Property, 810-812 Fifth Avenue penthouse, greenhouse, 1955-1957 (Box 20, Folder 249)
- Property, 810-812 Fifth Avenue penthouse, storeroom bookcases and racks, 1955-1960 (Box 20, Folder 250)
- Property, 811 Fifth Avenue Corporation, meetings and minutes, 1939-1945 (Box 20, Folder 251)
- Property, 811 Fifth Avenue Corporation, correspondence, 1938-1945 (Box 20, Folder 252)
- Property, 811 Fifth Avenue Corporation, correspondence on purchase of ground fee, 1940-1943 (Box 20, Folder 253)
- Property, 811 Fifth Avenue Corporation, correspondence, 1943-1949 (Box 20, Folder 254)
- Property, 811 Fifth Avenue Corporation, correspondence, 1950-1971 (Box 21, Folder 255)
- Property, 811 Fifth Avenue Corporation, meeting of December 12, 1960, fallout shelter discussion, 1960 August-December (Box 21, Folder 256)
- Property, 811 Fifth Avenue Corporation, financial statements, 1966, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 257)
- Property, 812 Fifth Avenue, china display cases, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 258)
- Property, 812 Fifth Avenue, The Fifth-Central Park Corporation, 1964-1971 (Box 21, Folder 259)
- Property, Pleasantville, NY, Davison property, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 260)
- Property, Pocantico Hills and Tarrytown, general information, 1949-1971 (Box 21, Folder 261)
- Property, Pocantico Hills estate, general correspondence, 1935-1970 (Box 21, Folder 262)
- Property, Pocantico Hills estate, general, lakes, 1950 (Box 21, Folder 263)
- Property, Pocantico Hills estate, general, grounds, 1932-1959 (Box 21, Folder 264)
- Property, Pocantico Hills estate, general, grounds, 1960-1971 (Box 21, Folder 265)
- Property, Pocantico Hills estate, general, grounds, 1960-1971 (Box 21, Folder 265a)
- Property, Pocantico Hills estate, "A Brief History of Pocantico Hills", 1958-1960 (Box 21, Folder 267)
- Property, NAR Farms, personnel: Ramon Oliveros (Box 55)